Yeah. Hey, Asan. Just just want to ask
about the decision. Congratulations and
welcome to Tampa. I'm sure you had other
offers and just curious what brought you
to Tampa and what you like about the
team you're joining.
>> The defense got the big dog up front. He
eats people, kills people, destroys
them. To be able to play next to him,
play off each other, I think is is
great. And to have the linebackers and
the secondary they have here is is
phenomenal.
>> Yeah. Is is it weird for you that you've
known Tampa as a division opponent? Is
that a strange thing or is that
something you'll get over pretty quickly
and it it's it's your team?
>> I'm already over it.
I'm already over it, man. It's a short
shortlived memory of Carolina.
>> Our next question will come from Rick
Straoud.
>> Steve, if I can unmute myself here.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yes, sir. I can hear you.
>> Hey, Sean. Hey. Uh just if you could
take us through the process. I mean I
don't know were you surprised you were
released? You obviously did better
contractually. Uh just what was that 24
48 hours like for you that whole
process?
>> Uh wasn't shocked. Um the whole thing
was uh to get traded. I had permission
to seek a trade and
>> teams were interested. So I knew that
the best option was to get released and
the team was
>> okay with that and they released me and
that's how this came all came about. is
and Tampa was one of the main teams. So
it was Tampa and San Fran and before I
like a seeking tra seeking trade and
they said hey we would love to have you.
So I was like I would love to play here.
So that's how it all became a thing.
>> And you've been you know you're one of
those guys that uh play equally snaps on
run versus pass. I mean just how have
you uh sort of evolved you know your
your game into just being that allaround
you know defensive lineman? Um, you
know, better with age. You know, I'm
like fine wine. The older I get, the
better I get. So, as you can see in my
whole career, the older I gotten, the
better I gotten, the more athletic I
gotten. So, that's just who I am and
what I believe in is taking care of my
body and doing the things the right way
and cuz I all I love to do is win. I
come from a place of just wanting to win
since I was a little kid. So, I I thrive
on that.
>> Appreciate it. Thanks.
>> Yes, sir. Our next question will come
from Evan Winter. If any media have
questions, please raise your hand.
>> Hey Asan, congrats on the deal, man. Uh,
I'm so glad you brought up Vita. That's
exactly what I wanted to ask about.
You're known for your power and your
violence and your strength as well. Just
what is that going to do for that
defensive line and how how does that,
you know, match up against opposing
offensive lines?
>> Well, for me, how I see it is free my
dog, let him eat. And so when he's
eating, you know what that does? They're
going to try to attack him. Freeze me
up. Now I get to eat. So we just feeding
feasting off each other. And having
other guys around that's that's not just
vet that that feast as well. So we all
know that in this game on a Dline
especially, you got to do your job
together. You got to dominate your box.
You got to dominate your job, your 101
that you have. So it frees up everybody
else to do their to win and to have the
defense that you want to have.
Scott Reynolds.
>> Hey Sean, can you hear me?
>> Yes, sir.
>> You play with kind of an ass kicker
mentality. Where does that come from?
>> Comes from a little kid that used to
they used to try to pick on for not
having anything, for being so poor. So,
you know what I did every day? Whoop
somebody ass. Every day. Every day you
said something, I'll beat out of you. So
that's where that came from. Even in
college, you joke around, I'm g I'm
gonna beat your ass. So that's just how
I became. And I played the same way on
the field. So then I was like, you know,
like people talk and try to do like
dirty stuff and I just got tired of it.
So I just started letting people have
it, you know, let them know that I'm
going to beat what I'm going to do, how
I'm going to do it. And I'm sorry for
cussing, but that's just
>> how I am. Please continue. And um I just
destroy like that's all it was as a kid
like how much
I guess if I could see mad like madness
I can create. So that's how I always saw
it.
>> And and on that note um do you find that
that playing style is contagious? Do you
feel like when you play with that type
of vigor that that kind of spreads along
the D line and your defense kind of like
takes on that personality too?
>> Oh yeah. You know, you got to embody it.
You know, your brothers see you out
there doing what you're doing, they
gonna want to do the same thing. You you
you show them and you're with them and
you right got their back, they're gonna
have the same thing. They have the same
attitude. You know, it's just how I've
always been. I I it always just, you
know, just rubs off on people because
that's just how we got to play this
game. We want to be the defense we want
to be. We got to show everybody how we
are every single day, every play, every
minute, every second, and talk it and be
about it. You got to walk the walk as
well. You can't just talk it. You got to
walk the walk.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
>> Yes, sir.
>> General Lane.
>> Uh, how do I unmute myself? It's not
giving me the option to unmute.
>> Oh, okay. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry, I thought
I had to manually unmute. Um, no, I I
really um I appreciate the honesty even
with the cursing. I think it's great.
Um,
I'm curious if if you had any moments in
your career where you felt like you were
underestimated out on the field or your
opponent was talking a lot of trash and
like you felt like you really stepped up
in that moment and kicked ass as as you
spoke about.
>> I have many of those moments. I can give
you one uh AFC championship against San
Francisco. If you go back and watch that
game, you'll see why I am. But anyways,
not even it's not even just that. Like
me starting from where I got drafted, I
always wore that chip on my shoulder. So
that disrespect's always been with me my
whole career. So every time I step on
the field is to show people that
disrespect ain't real. So I don't, you
know, people say they like my game now
or all that stuff. I don't really care.
That chip's going to forever be there
until I retire. That that disrespect is
is who I am and why I live and play the
way I am.
>> And if I can ask a followup, you've
played in a lot of different defenses
and obviously Todd BS is known for being
really multiple. How can that help as
you enter this defense? Um, you know, I
mean, I'll say
just understanding the nuances of a
defense and knowing how you can take
your game to the next level and knowing
that when you can take your shots and
telling your brothers and understanding
that that familiarity of how you see
things and how they see things and
receiving and knowing like how they move
and how they disrupt plays when they see
certain inside zones or counters. or
outsides and really having a coach that
can put you in certain many different
situations and opportunities to thrive.
That's great. You know, as a defensive
lineman, that's what you want. You know,
you don't want to be so uh what is it?
Stagnant where you're just stuck in the
same place. And you know, you want to be
able to be able to move around and see
different looks and see so they don't
see you and pinpoint you in one spot.
You can really just get after it and
understand how you can destroy things.
Thank you.
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Greg Almond.
>> Hey Sean, I'm I'm curious to to to see
your fit in this defense. Obviously, you
could play alongside Vita. You could
play in place of Vita. Um I I guess you
I don't know if you're more natural as a
nose, as a five. Where do you think you
fit in? Where are you most comfortable?
>> Anywhere.
>> That's a good answer. Thank you, man.
>> You're welcome.
Scott Reynolds.
>> Aan, you were part of a Panthers team
that ripped away the NFC South title
from Tampa Bay. Now that you're with the
Buccaneers and be will be facing the
Panthers twice. What are your thoughts
on that? And and do you believe that you
are the guy that can help the NFC South
title return back to Tampa Bay?
>> I don't think it's just one guy. It's a
team effort. I think that my personality
and my what I give off and my energy and
how I play can help. I don't think it
just takes one guy, takes a team and
clearly the organization knows that. So
they've done everything they they needed
to do whatever they whoever they need to
get and bring them in. So I'm just a
piece of that pie, you know. So I never
think of it as just myself. There's not
no myself. There's no I in team. So it's
a that's how I always think of it. So,
it's not just
>> how I think, it's how how we all think
together of doing this winning back.
>> You've been in the league a long time. I
I don't know if you don't think you've
played necessarily with Alexandone or
with Alquedian Mohamad, but um you've
probably seen their games or know a
little bit about their games. What do
you think about your new teammates?
>> They play the same way I play. Nasty,
physical, and they're about action. So,
>> that's what I like to see. They know the
game. They understand. They understand
when to take the points. what his team's
doing, the opponent team's trying to do
to them, like all that. Like they
understand the game of football and
having teammates understand football is
a great mind to have together.
>> Yeah. Thank you.
>> You're welcome.
>> Evan Winter.
>> Hey Sean, this intensity that you bring,
I mean, even in this pressure right now,
man, the Bucks really needed that last
year. They even brought in Jason Pierre
Paul to try to, you know, get a little
bit of a jump start in the locker room
and whatnot. Um, how do you make sure
that the teammates around you that are
you leading by actions more than words
or vice versa when it comes to getting
guys to gravitate around that? All the
above.
>> Coming together, going to eat, having
things, having a chef pull up, having
food trucks pull up, going to have going
to events, creating events for each
other. It's just knowing that you can
trust your brother, knowing that he has
your back no matter what, and he can
speak to him about anything. He's he's
telling you about his life that he has
and the things that went on his and that
all those all those things and those
moments all matter. Like that's how you
connect with your brothers. That's how
you come close. And that's, you know,
it's we don't get these deals to be
selfish. We get these deals and things
that we get to to help one another to
excel. So we can excel as a team. So I
always seen it as how we can excel. I've
had great leaders in my in my past that
done the same exact thing and I really
appreciate them because they showed me
the way of how you do certain things and
that's how I've always and I live by
since that moment forward from from
those days back when I was younger. Who
are, if you can name names, who are some
of those guys that that showed you?
>> Heldinatada, Dwight Freeny, um, Snacks
Harrison, Damen Snacks, Harrison, AD,
um, Brock, uh, shoot, even my brother
that's the same age as me. Like, we've
we talked like he's done a lot, though.
Jaylen Ramsey, like, he's he like we
it's a lot of guys that's done a lot of
things. Like, Stafford used to do those
things back in the day, back when we
were in Detroit. Like, you have those
guys. You have DeAndre Levy, Grover
Quinn, like Slay. Like I had all those
guys give me gems since I was a young
buck. And like they knew what motivated
me, what didn't motivate, how to
motivate you to to to really do things,
not just about the money, but to do
things together, not for yourself. So
that's why I really appreciate and the
life lessons and things they taught me.
>> That's awesome, man. Thank you.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Our last question will come from Jenna
Lane.
Um, culture is so big with any
organization and obviously you were part
of a winning culture when you were with
the Rams and you've also been part of
some teams that had struggled like what
do you really feel like sets apart a
Super Bowl winning locker room and what
can like how can you bring that uh to
Tampa cuz because they've lost a lot of
the pieces that were part of their Super
Bowl run in 2020. Uh just doing things
and knowing that we have each other's
back. Like doing going the extra mile,
doing things together. Not like I said,
not alone. Like no one's alone in this.
This is a team game. So your best player
has to be the same player that's with
everyone that's trying to make bring
along the the weakness of the team. So
like just making sure you have all those
pieces and everyone together, not just
from the coaches, from a player
standpoint, because the players, we're
the ones that's out there. the coach
only can tell us so much and everybody
else can like tell us, but we're the
ones out there. So, we got to be able to
to understand and affect it together,
not so that's how it's always been for
me and that's how I've always seen it
done to get the job that you want to get
done to win.
>> Thanks so much.
>> Welcome.
>> All right, that's all we have time for.
Thanks everyone. Thanks Aan.
>> Thank you. Nice see nice meeting you
guys.